// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is Unix?",
    answer: "Unix is an operating system",
    options: [
      "Unix is a programming language",
      "Unix is a software program",
      "Unix is an operating system",
      " Unix is a text editor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The Unix shell is both _______ and _______ language.",
    answer: "scripting, interpreter",
    options: [
      "scripting, interpreter",
      "high level, low level",
      "interactive, responsive",
      "interpreter, executing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In which language UNIX is written?",
    answer: "C",
    options: [
      "Java",
      "Python",
      "C++",
      "C"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is the first UNIX editor?",
    answer: "ed",
    options: [
      "ex",
      "ed",
      "vi",
      "emacs"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a feature of Unix?",
    answer: "easy to use",
    options: [
      "multiuser",
      "multitasking",
      "easy to use",
      "portability"
    ]
  },
  

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which editor is used by the Unix system to edit files?",
    answer: "vi",
    options: [
      "vi",
      "word",
      "notepad",
      "notepad++"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which part of the Unix operating system interacts with the hardware?",
    answer: "kernel",
    options: [
      "application program",
      "vi editor",
      "kernel",
      "shell"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which command is used to display the documentation of commands in Unix?",
    answer: "man",
    options: [
      "whatis",
      "man",
      "help",
      "search"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which Unix command is used for changing the current directory?",
    answer: "cd",
    options: [
      "rm",
      "cd",
      "pwd",
      "cp"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which command is used for printing the current working directory?",
    answer: "pwd",
    options: [
      "dir",
      "home",
      "cd",
      "pwd"
    ]
  },
  
];